Question 1.

Consider the following pattern: 
A → D M → P X → A  a → d m → p x → a 
Now, write a program to solve the following message using Python, JavaScript or Ruby.  
Vrphwklqj phdqlqjixo 
Hint: The answer is something meaningful. 
 
Question 2.  
  
Use the following paragraphs (in italics below) as input to the program you wrote for Question 1.
It should output a meaningful question. Write a program to solve that question. 

Zulwh d surjudp (lq Sbwkrq, MdydVfulsw ru Uxeb) wr srsxodwh dqg wkhq vruw d  udqgrpob glvwulexwhg 
olvw ri 1 ploolrq lqwhjhuv, hdfk lqwhjhu kdylqj d ydoxh >= 1 dqg <=  100 zlwkrxw xvlqj dqb exlowlq/hawhuqdo 
oleudub/ixqfwlrq iru vruwlqj. 
Brxu surjudp vkrxog fduhixoob frqvlghu wkh lqsxw dqg frph xs zlwk wkh prvw hiilflhqw  vruwlqj vroxwlrq brx fdq wklqn ri. 
Surylgh wkh vsdfh dqg wlph frpsohalwb ri brxu dojrulwkp 